<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Ben's homepage</title><link>https://ankel.github.io/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Ben's homepage</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:22:33 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ankel.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Switching to "stack" theme.</title><link>https://ankel.github.io/p/switching-to-stack-theme./</link><pubDate>Sat, 31 Jan 2026 11:22:33 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankel.github.io/p/switching-to-stack-theme./</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;The paper theme is a bit blank, and I also don&amp;rsquo;t like their look on mobile. So I started looking around and I found &lt;a class="link" href="https://stack.jimmycai.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
 &gt;Stack&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has enough configuration to keep me busy for a while, but on first look, it&amp;rsquo;s not as complicated as some of the more crazy ones out there.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So how do I look?&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Wealth Simulator</title><link>https://ankel.github.io/p/wealth-simulator/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 22:33:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankel.github.io/p/wealth-simulator/</guid><description>&lt;img src="https://ankel.github.io/" alt="Featured image of post Wealth Simulator" /&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent a weekend (one afternoon and one morning, to be specific) playing with Gemini. The result: &lt;a class="link" href="https://ankel.github.io/wealth-simulator/" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
 &gt;Wealth Simulator&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The goal of this app is to run 1,000 iteration of Monte Carlo simulation to see how the future may play out, based on some provided inputs. The inputs are rather straightforward but do let me know if anything can be improved.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="build-and-deploy"&gt;Build and Deploy
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The app is written as a single React app, and deployed as a static site on Github Pages. The build and deployment is automated through &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/ankel/ankel.github.io/blob/cb48b711587796187101fd97522ea7aa38cf5eaa/.github/workflows/deploy-site-wealth-simulator.yaml" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
 &gt;Github Action&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Hello World</title><link>https://ankel.github.io/p/hello-world/</link><pubDate>Sun, 18 Jan 2026 19:44:46 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://ankel.github.io/p/hello-world/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;This repository was created three years ago. Three years, and I finally gotten around to actually build the website out of it :D&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="setup-overview"&gt;Setup overview
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;The site is generated using Hugo. The Hugo content is stored under &lt;code&gt;/docs&lt;/code&gt; folder. Each commit to &lt;code&gt;main&lt;/code&gt; branch triggers a github action to build and push the page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The Github action YAML is straightforward enough. The most tricky line is perharp the &lt;code&gt;publish_dir: ./docs/public&lt;/code&gt;. This copy the content of the right place where Hugo built the site. Took me 4-5 tries to figured that out (reading the build output was very helpful!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id="hugo-configuration"&gt;Hugo configuration
&lt;/h2&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hugo out of the box uses TOML (though it can also support YAML and JSON). These days, my editor of choice is VS code. And it&amp;rsquo;s a bit mind-blowing to discover that VS code out of the box does not support TOML.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have written too much YAML (and hated every minute of it), but the alternative is to install and 3rd party plugin for TOML support - which, as of right now, is &lt;a class="link" href="https://github.com/tamasfe/taplo" target="_blank" rel="noopener"
 &gt;this one&lt;/a&gt;. Decisions, decisions, decisions&amp;hellip;.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>